UNITE Assistant to the President Alan Howard Files 6000/029
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
UNITE Assistant to the President Alan Howard Files
1991-2000
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Howard, Alan
6000/029
6.5 cubic feet
6.5 linear ft.
Records.
This collection includes materials of the Industrial Ladies Garment Workers Union (ILGWU). Materials are unprocessed.
6766683
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives 227 Ives Hall Tower Road Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheelref@cornell.edu https://catherwood.library.cornell.edu/kheel/
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 02, 2012
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, February 17, 2016
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6000/048: UNITE Executive Assistant to the President David Melman Papers 6000 AV: UNITE Audio-Visual Collection 6000 G: UNITE Posters 6000 MB: UNITE Memorabilia 6000 P: UNITE Photographs 6000 PUBS: UNITE Publications
Clothing workers -- Labor unions -- New York (State); Clothing trade -- New York (State); Howard, Alan; Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union; Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees
6766683
- El Salvador, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  Spanish, English
- El Salvador: Trip, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  Spanish, English. July 10-13, 1997.
- Articles Re: El Salvador, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- CIPAF, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- DR: Bonahan, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Philips-Van Heusen, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Guatemala/PVH/Contract, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- DR: Fenatrazonas, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Cambodia, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- CTU, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  Spanish
- Costa Rica/ ANTEF, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- CIPAF Project Update, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  Spanish, English August 1996.
- China, 1993-1997 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- China Studies, 1995-1997 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Ann Taylor, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Nicaragua, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Nicaragua, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Mexico, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Mexico, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- GLEP, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  December 1995.
- GLEP, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- GLEP, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Guatemala, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Cuba, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- El Salvador, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- El Salvador, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- DR: Trip, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  Spanish, English. January 1996.
- Montreal Re: DR, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  October 1997.
- Han Chang, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Bonahan-Strike, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Dominican Republic, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Dominican Republic, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Dominican Republic, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- El Salvador, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Guatemala/PVH, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Sears, Roebuck, and Co., 1996 (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Auto Parts, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- ACTWU/Industrial Data, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Italian Americans, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  December 12, 1995.
- Merger/ Media, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- National Labor Committee: Income/Salary Data, 1994-1996 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- National Labor Committee: Day of Conscience, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Codes of Conduct, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- ITGLWF, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Child Labor, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Sempo, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- AFL-CIO, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Firm Analysis, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- International Labor Rights Fund, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- ILRF, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- ILREF, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- ILO, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- ILFTU, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Human Rights Watch, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Human Rights Watch, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Global Exchange7, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- National Labor Committee: Board of Director Packet, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- National Labor Committee, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- National Labor Committee, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- National Labor Committee, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Regional Coordination, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- National Retail Federation, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Claiborne, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- The Limited, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Levi, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  July 1997.
- Levi, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Nike, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Levi, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Warnaco, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Warnaco, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- VF, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- May Company, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Pendleton, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  January 1997.
- Marymount University, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 39)
- Marshalls, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 40)
- Claiborne Contracts, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Clairborne Code of Conduct, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 42)
- FITTVCC, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 43)
- FITTVCC, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 44)
- Copenhagen, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 45)
- Buchanan, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 46)
- Walmart, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 47)
- Verite', 1995-1997 (Box 2, Folder 48)
- Reebok, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 49)
- General Articles (Bad), 1997 (Box 2, Folder 50)
- ITLWF: FITTVCC Project, 1995-1997 (Box 2, Folder 51)
- Reginal Meetings, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 52)
- Sweatshops, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Sweatshops, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Articles by Jay Mazur, 1992-1997 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Kearney, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Arnold & Porter, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- W.H. Phase, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- NCL/AIP, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Papers, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- FLA White House - related, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- White H. Confirmation, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- 4/14 White House, 1995-1997 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- AFL-CIO, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Labor, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- White House 1, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- W.H. 11/11, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- White House, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  January 9, 1997.
- White House Meeting, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  September 26, 1997.
- White House, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  November 1996.
- White House, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  December 1996.
- L.L. Bean Meeting, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- White House Meeting, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  August 5, 1997.
- Association Models, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- W.H. 3/2, 1994-1998 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- White House 4, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Guatemala/PVH: Camosa Contract, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Guatemala, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Phillips-Van Heusen (Negotiations), 1997 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Phillips-Van Heusen (Corporate), 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- South Africa, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Saipan, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Honduras, 1995-1996 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Honduras, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Disney, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Dillard Department Store, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Notes re: Honduras, Guatemala, and El Salvador, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  July 8, 1997.
- Honduras 3H:, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Kellwood, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- GAP, 1995-1996 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Esprit, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Research/Region, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Southern Africa, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Jamaica, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Honduras: Kimi, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Continental Park, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Kmart, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Kathie Lee, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 30)
- Kathie Lee, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- J.C. Penny, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Guess: Mexico, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 33)
- Guess, 1994-1997 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Federated, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- The Dress Barn, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Disney, 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Guatemala: GSP, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Guatemala: GSP, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Comez/GLEP, 1995-1997 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Korea Re: DR, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Korea, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Korea, 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Panama/Klein, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Honduras: Trip, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Honduras - Yu Hwa, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Haiti 7, 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- GLEP Press Reports/Articles, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Guatemala: USTR, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Mark Barenberg, 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Miscellaneous: Meeting Notes, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Miscellaneous Articles, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Pena Gomez, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Flor, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Caribbean Basin Initiative, 1995-1997 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- CBI Strategies, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- CBI, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- BSR, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- National Labor Committee, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- American Institute for Free Labor Development, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- AIP, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- AIP, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- AFL-CIO, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Robert B. Reich, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  June 16,1996.
- El Salvador Discussion Marzo 20, Grupo Centra, Gilberto G.D., 2000 (Box 5, Folder 32)
- San Salvador, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 33)
- Cuba, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 34)
- Eliecer Sanchez Castillo Costa Rica, 1998-1999 (Box 5, Folder 35)
- Liz Clairborne Code of Conduct, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 36)
- Fortuna Calvo, 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 37)
- Luis Anderson (Venezuela), 1999 (Box 5, Folder 38)
- Mayra Jimenez, 1997-1999 (Box 5, Folder 39)
- Alan Howard's Articles, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 40)
- Fund Relief, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 41)
- Hurricane Relief, 1998-1999 (Box 5, Folder 42)
- Mei Yeung Fong, 1998-1999 (Box 5, Folder 43)
- Honduras, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 44)
- Stan Gasek, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 45)
- Haiti Support Network, 1997-1999 (Box 5, Folder 46)
- Guatemala, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 47)
- Steve Coats Guatemala Labor Education Project, 1997-1999 (Box 5, Folder 48)
- Uruguay Geraldo Iglesias, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 49)
- William Busis, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 50)
- Heather White Verite, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 51)
- Dr. Jorge A. Subero Republica Domincana, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 52)
- Dr. Ralph Alburquerque Domincan Republic, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 53)
- Jacobo Ramos Federacion Trabajadores Dominicanos, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Jose Ramirez, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Magaly Pineda, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Pedro Ortega, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Witness for Peace Nicaragua, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Al Moore, 1997-1999 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Roque Feliz Mendez Codigo de Conducta - DR, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Maria Luz Translations, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Voucher Copies, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  June 1996.
- Contracts, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- GEB, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  October 1996.
- GEB, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  May 6, 1996.
- GEB, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  June 17, 1996.
- GEB, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Ex Comic - AFL-CIO, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  January 1996.
- Staff Mtgs, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- ICCR, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- USTR, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Kantor, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- AFL-CIO Int/Org, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Adidas - Copenhagen, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Toys, 1995-1996 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- AFL-CIO Politics, 1991-1995 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Los Angeles, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- CMA 5/17 A.M, 1993-1996 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- AFOL-CIO Survey, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Bruce Fieldman, 1995-1997 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Claiborne 5, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Claiborne: Summary of Audit Charges, 1993-1995 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Claiborne: Code of Conduct5, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Levi, 1993-1995 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Copenhagen Meeting, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  October 4-6, 1995.
- AFL-CIO Convention, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 9)